webparx.com 2015-11-05

# Privacy Policy - Webparx.com

**We are concerned seriously about the privacy of our users.** Please read this Privacy Policy to know more about how we treat individually identifiable details and information. We bestow this Privacy Policy as you have the right to know what knowledge and information we garner, how it is preserved and utilized, and under which circumstances it may be revealed. If you have suggestions, comments, questions, or any concerns about our Privacy Policy, kindly contact us via email at  **contact@avantplex.com**  or in write to us at: Privacy Director, AVANTPLEX Media

**Online Privacy Standards.**  Although there are no such official standards administrating privacy practices on the web or internet, we firmly follow the principles promoted by the Federal Trade Commission’s Fair Information Practices Principles, presently available at [http://www.ftc.gov/reports/privacy3/toc.htm](https://www.ftc.gov/site-information/privacy-policy).

**What This Policy Subsumes.**  This policy subsumes Avantplex media’s treatment of personally recognizable information that we acquire when you use our services or visit our website. We consider personally recognizable information as the information that anyone can use to recognize or contact you in person, such as real name, personal telephone number, date of birth, email address, or physical contact address. Information and details that we use inwardly to recognize you as a member in our website or system, such as your selected UserID which is not concerned personally recognizable information.

**What This Policy Does Not Subsumes.**  This policy does not subsumes the privacy practices on behalf of third parties that doesn’t belongs to us or we don’t rule or control, such as our advertisers and associates. Moreover, we may proffer links to other services and to other sites occasionally that may attract you. All of these sites function independently of AVANTPLEX and they have their own privacy or security terms and practices. For your smooth and quality on-line experience, we embolden you to analyze their policies before submitting any personal details or information to them.

### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

**Registration Information.**  During the registration phenomena, we garner your email address. We will send you an email with a link to verify that own the provided email address. You will have to choose a UserID that we will use to recognize you in our system.

**Optional Member Profile Information.**  You can opt to provide us with added optional details about yourself, to help us convey a more personalized experience to you. You can also opt to provide us with information that you use to access the web services of our partners, i.e. your username or password for certain photo-sharing and instant messaging services. We make use of this information to get the easy access to your favorite services throughout our website.

**Access to Your Personal Information.**  Generally, we make it effortless for you to view the personally recognizable information that we have collected from you in your member profile page, where you can edit, add or delete it according to your favour.

### INFORMATION WE DO NOT COLLECT

**Children.**  As described further in our Terms of Service, presently available at <http://www.webparx.com/terms-of-use> you must be 13 years of age or older to register to use our website. Hence, we do not intentionally garner personally recognizable information about children. If you trust that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please inform us by email at contact@avantplex.com or write to our Privacy Director at the address noted above.

**Social Security Number.**  We don’t ask for or need your social security number to make use any of our services or to get access to any part of our site.

### INFORMATION WE TRACK

**Log Files.**  Alike many websites, we collect some anonymous, non-personal details automatically and store it in our web server log files. This details includes internet protocol addresses, internet service provider (ISP), browser type, site entry/exit pages, date/time stamp, operating system, and click stream data. We use this information for improvement our site, analyzing trends, regulate the site, track the users’ activities around the site, and gather comprehensive information about our user base as entire. Comprehensive information is data we gather about a group or a category of services or members from which single member identities have been eliminated, and therefore does not involve your personally recognizable information.

**Cookies.**  A cookie is a tiny text file that is reserved on a user’s computer for track record-keeping purposes. It also helps us to understand how our site visitants click on to our site, and what pages they observe or look into during their visit. Alike many websites, we reserve an encrypted/encipher cookie on your computer so that we can recognize you when you come back to our website without needing you to log-in every time. Cookies also help in tracking and understanding the interests of our users, enhancing the overall experience of our site.

**Our partners.**  Some of our business partners can also make use of cookies on our site. For an example, some of our advertising associates may use cookies to garner non-personally recognizable information about your visit to our site for providing advertisements about goods, products and services that may be interest you. We have no control over or access to these cookies, and, this privacy policy does not rule the use of cookies by our business associates or advertisers. To be eliminated from these services, please visit some of our partners’ websites and follow the following instructions.

  * Google: [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads)
  * Network Advertising Initiative: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

You can settle your web browser software to enfeeble/disable cookies. For doing this, please refer to the help option of your specific browser for more information on how to disable or manage cookies. Disabling cookies, can still let you to view our site, but some sections of our site will not work properly.

### HOW WE USE INFORMATION IN COMPANY COMMUNICATIONS

We use emails and/or eminent notifications on our websites as our ultimate means to notify our members of necessary service and promotional declarations.

**Service-related Declarations.**  We use your email address to distribute necessary service-related declarations. Example, service-related declarations includes email verification during registration process, requests for reset of password, important security or maintenance of server updates, software updates and upgrades, and new releases or policy alterations. These service-related declarations are reviews as a crucial part of our web service, and members cannot skip these email declarations.

**Promotional Declarations.**  For improving the experience for our users, we will proffer you the facility to sign up for optional email communications, such as frequent updates from our corporate website, or email alerts and newsletters for particular web guidance. These communications are improvements to our service and are totally optional. We will ask for your agreement before sending you advertising communications, and will make it effortless for you to unsubscribe from these communications, either by emails or though your member profile page.

**Refer A Friend Program.**  If you opt for using our reference service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. Then instantly an email will be sent inviting him or her to visit the site. We reserve this information for the only purpose of sending this one-time email, and to record the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at contact@avantplex.com for requesting that we eliminate this information from our database.

### ON OUR WEBSITE

**Identification of Authors by UserID.**  We are a cooperative media company, which means we rely on the grants, donations and actions of our members to enhance the quality of the website experience. When you take other important activities on the website, such as editing or deleting someone else’s content or messaging, you will be recognized as the author of that action and in these circumstances, you will be only identified by your UserID. In some cases you can opt to include other personally recognizable information along with your UserID citations, like your instant messaging username.

**Public Profile.**  When you register, we will generate a public member profile based on your UserID. You will get the option to include your personally recognizable information in your public profile, but you are not needed to do so. You can easily edit, add and delete information in your public profile through the member profile page.

**Site Statistics.** We use details and information gathered from our web log files to measure and publish anonymous, non-personal, cumulative statistics that we believe our members are keen to view.

### FOR INTERNAL REPORTING AND SCRUTINY

We use information collected from log files and cookies to enhance our website, scrutinize trends, govern the site, track users’ activities around the site, and to gather cumulative information about our user base entirely. We do not tie this data to personally recognizable information.

### HOW WE SHARE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE

**Public Messages.**  Some of the features of our website, like the group blog and forums, allow you to interact with other members by submitting public messages. Please be receptive and aware about what you write in these public messages as they can be viewed, garnered or used by any visitors of our website. We are totally not responsible for any personally recognizable information that you post or permit others to post through public messages.

### WITH THIRD-PARTIES

**Sharing, Renting, and Selling Information We Collect.**  We will neither rent nor sell your personally identifiable information to anyone. Occasionally we share anonymous, non-personal, aggregate information about our user base with partners or advertisers, and we may publish these aggregate usage statistics on our website for the interest of our members. We do not tie this shared or published data to personally identifiable information.

**Linked Services.**  In few cases, we permit you to get access or link to other web services through our website. We make it effortless for you to resolve when you are accessing or linking to those other web services through our website. In all of these cases, our associates may choose to garner your personal information as they consider it appropriate. We are not responsible for or in control of how our associates use, gather or reveal your information acquired through these linked services. We advise you to be aware when you use these partner services and, for your best on-line experience, we advise you to consider their policies before posting any personal information to them.

### AS NECESSARY IN LEGAL CASES

**Legal Obligations.**  We store the right to reveal your personally recognizable information as needed by law and when we believe that revelation is important for the protection our rights and/or to abide by a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal procedure served on our website.

**Procurement.**  If our company is obtained, all of our resources and assets, involving user details and information, may be transmitted to the obtaining company. At that time, your user information may become subject to the obtaining company’s privacy policy. Before we sync your user information, we will inform you either by email or by posting n eminent notice on our site, and we will help you to remind of your ability to edit, add or delete your personally recognizable information from your member profile page in advance of any such sync of personal information to them.

### HOW WE KEEP INFORMATION SECURE

**Security of Account Information.**  Your account information is completely password-protected. We will never share your password with anyone. Please do not disclose to or share your password with anyone, and better change your password from time to time, to keep your account information intact and secured.

**Network Security.**  We have enforced various commercially standard security technologies and methods to protect information, which includes your personal information, reserved in our computer systems from unauthorized access. Please be cognizant of and aware that no procedure of transfer over the internet, or procedure of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

**Management Procedures.**  We also sustain standard physical and electronic methodological safeguards that restrict access to your personally recognizable information to our agents (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who, through the course of standard business activities, require to access your personally recognizable information.

### YOUR PERSONAL CHOICES

**Revealing Information to Other Members.**  You are fully able to regulate what personal information about you is shared, revealed or allocated with other members in your public profile page, and what details and information you choose to keep confidential and private. You can add, view, edit, and delete information in your public profile through your member profile page.

**Receiving Communications.**  If you subscribe or enable to any optional advertising communications, you will also be able to unsubscribe from them through your member profile page or through the emails sent from us.

**Editing / Deleting Member Account Details** **.**  You are allowed to view the personally recognizable information we have garnered from you in your member profile page where you can edit, add, or delete according to your favour. You may also request for the deletion of your member account through your member profile page.

### UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

**On a regular basis, we will consider and make changes to our privacy policy with specific interval.**  When we do so, we will inform you either by email or by placing an eminent notice on our website. The most latest version of our privacy policy is always available from a link on our homepage, and at <http://www.webparx.com/privacy-policy>.
